Guide to the Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
- Series VIII: Boston Under Raymond Flynn
  - A Touch of Class. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 4, No. 6, 1985., Jun. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Lukas, J. Anthony
    Journal article, 5 pages
  - Turning Midtown around: The unveiling of Coyle's dream city. Boston, MA: The Boston Phoenix, 1988., May-88 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Dezell, Maureen
    Newspaper article, 13 pages
  - A neighborhood reborn. Boston, MA: Boston Globe Magazine, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Radin, Charles
    Magazine article with margin notes, 7 pages
  - The New Populists. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 4, No. 7, 1985., Jul. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Journal article on Ray Flynn and Mario Cuomo, 13 pages.
  - Still With Flynn. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 9, 1983., Nov. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Journal article, 9 pages.
  - Ray Flynn, A Shy Hero. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 5, 1983., Jul. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Pearlstein, Steven; Lydon, Christopher
    Journal articles, 6 pages.
  - Boston's Political Revival. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 6, 1983., Aug. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - A Black Mayor for Boston?. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 2, 1983., Apr. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Hill, Tony
    Journal article, 10 pages
  - BOSS?. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 1, No. 5, 1982., May, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Whitehead, Ralph
    Journal article, 4 pages
  - Who Speaks for Boston Blacks?. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 1, No. 9, 1982., Jul. 1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Journal article,4 pages
  - After Kevin, Who?. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 1, No. 8, 1982., Jun. 1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Jones, DeWitt; Lydon, Christopher; Minicucci, Stephen
  - Flawed Hero, Final Act. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2. No. 1, 1983., Mar. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Carroll, James
    Journal article, 6 pages
  - Terrymandering - The politics and the law behind Boston's election year snafu. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 7, 1983., Sept. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Sheehan, Thomas; Pearlstein, Stephen
    Journal article, 8 pages
  - Handicapping the Mayor's Race. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 8, 1983., Oct. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Driscoll, Thomas; Zabierek, Mark
  - Remembering Kevin. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 10, 1983., Dec. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Smith, Rick
  - Letters to the editor. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 3, No. 1, 1984., Jan. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Author: Various authors
  - Opinion columns on Dukakis and King. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 2, No. 3, 1983., May-83 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Journal articles, 4 pages
  - Is Kevin Losing His Grip on The BRA?. Boston, MA: The Boston Observer, 3, No. 3, 1984., Mar. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Journal article, 2 pages
  - Martha on Menino' - Various Bay State Banner and Globe articles collected from online database. Boston, MA: Banner and Globe, 1994 - 2006., 1994 - 2006 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    Newspaper articles
  - Blackout. Boston, MA: Boston Globe Magazine, 84, No. 1, 1992., Jan. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Strahinich, John
    Magazine article on black politicians in Boston, the effects of Charles Stuart, 5 pages.
  - Childish Ideas - Beyond the Midtown day-care debate. Boston, MA: Boston Phoenix, 1988., Dec. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Newspaper article, 5 pages
  - Year of the choice - Taking the China out of Chinatown?. Boston, MA: Boston Phoenix, 1988., Sept. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Flynn, Sean
    Newspaper article, 8 pages
  - After hitting the Fan - What's next for the pier?. Boston, MA: Boston Phoenix, 1988., Jan. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Medearis, John
    Newspaper article, 7 pages
  - Roxbury fears displacement. Boston, MA: Boston Ledger, 1985., Jul. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Holland, Coria
  - Pierce Building Development Ready to Go. Boston, MA: Dorchester Citizen, 1984., Jun. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Lovett, Chris
    Newspaper article, 2 pages
  - 1010 Mass. Ave Development Spurs Interest Toward New Market Revitalization District. Boston, MA: South End News, 1984., Apr. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Jourgensen, Thor
    Newspaper article, 1 pages
  - East Broadway Earns Card Designation. Boston, MA: South Boston Tribune, 46, No. 37, 1984., Jun. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: [author unknown]
  - Poverty and Power. Boston, MA: Boston Review, 1994., Jun. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Jennings, James
    Journal article, 1 page
  - Implementing urban waterfront redevelopment in an historic context: a case study of The Boston Naval Shipyard. Kingston, ON: Queen's University - School of Urban and Regional Planning, 1999., Oct. 1999 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Gordon, David
    Journal article from online source, 15 pages
  - Urban Planning, Community Participation, and the Roxbury Master Plan in Boston. AAPSS, 2004., Jul. 2004 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Journal article, 20 pages
  - Rebuilding Boston. Boston, MA: Boston Review, 1994., Jun. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - A Challenge to the Racial Order: Boston's Latino Community. Boston, MA: Boston Review, 1992., Sept. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Uriarte, Miren
  - Back Home and on the Run. National Journal, 30, No. 22, 1998., May-98 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Germond, Jack; Witcover, Jules
  - Leftward ho!. Boston, MA: Boston Phoenix, 1999., Sept. 1999 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Geman, Ben
  - The dealmaker. Boston, MA: Boston Globe Magazine, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Cassidy, Tina
    Magazine article, 13 pages
  - Getting Their Fair Share. Boston, MA: Boston Globe Magazine, 1981., Jun. 1981 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Magazine article, 7 pages
  - Mayor's linkage plan draws mixed reviews. Boston, MA: Bay State Banner, 1985., Nov. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Elliott, Clinton
  - Neighborhood Councils Would Make Decisions About Development Under Proposed Law. Boston, MA: Jamaica Plain Citizen, 1989., Mar. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Storey, Sandra
  - Complex Development Issues Affect Neighborhood Life. Boston, MA: Jamaica Plain Citizen, 1989., Apr. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Power to the neighborhoods. Boston, MA: Boston Ledger, 1989., Apr. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Tehan, Glenn
    Newspaper article
  - Neighborhood council plan sparks debate. Boston, MA: Boston Herald, 1989., Apr. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Author: Sciacca, Joe
  - Neighborhoods Convention Draws 500. Boston, MA: Jamaica Plain Citizen, 1989., Apr. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Executive and Legislative Summaries of CCCD Home Rule Petition. Boston, MA: CCCD, 1988., Sept. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Author: CCCD
    Document outlining neighborhood council roles and duties, 3 pages
  - FAQ about Coalition for Community Control of Development. Boston, MA: CCCD, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Document answering simple questions on CCCD's abilities, 3 pages
  - State of the Neighborhoods Convention - Agenda. Boston, MA: CCA,CCCD, Episcopal City Mission, 1989., Apr. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Author: CCA, CCCD, Episcopal City Mission
    Pamphlet with convention agenda, 3 pages
  - Community Control of Development. Boston, MA: City Issues - The Newsletter of The Episcopal City Mission, 5, No.1, 1989., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Author: Episcopal City Mission
    Newsletter, 20 pages
  - Boston Gives Residents Voice on Local Decisions. Boston, MA: The Neighborhood Works, 12, No. 6, 1990., Jan. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Author: Devine, Kevin
  - The Politics of Economic Development Planning: Boston in the 1980s. Boston, MA: MIT, 1987., Jun. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    Author: Ehrlich, Bruce
    Masters thesis, 120 pages
  - Dancing with the City: The Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative and Land Control in Roxbury. Boston, MA: UMASS, 1991., Jun. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    Author: Alicea, Jose Antonio
    Masters thesis, 137 pages
  - Who Rules Boston? - A Citizen's Guide to Reclaiming the City. Boston, MA: Boston Urban Study Group, 1984., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    Author: Harrington, Michael; Boston Urban Study Group
    Booklet, 115 pages
  - Downtown Development and Urban Reform - The Politics of Boston's Linkage Policy. Urban Affairs Quaterly, 26, No. 3, 1991., Mar. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    Author: Dreier, Peter; Ehrlich, Bruce
  - The Limits of Localism - Progressive Housing Policies in Boston, 1984 - 1989. Urban Affairs Quaterly, 26, No. 2, 1990., Dec. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    Author: Dreier, Peter; Keating, Dennis
    Journal article, 24 pages
  - Ray Flynn's Legacy - Draft. 1993., Jun. 1993 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    Author: Dreier, Peter
    Draft paper, 25 pages
  - Redlining Cities: How Banks Color Community Development. Challenge, 1991., Dec. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Community-based Housing: A New Direction in Federal Housing Policy. Shelterforce, 1987., Oct. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Boston: a choice for change. Perspectives - In These Times, 1983., Sept. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Linking Downtown Development to Broader Community Goals - An Analysis of Linkage Policy in Three Cities. APA Journal, 52, No. 2, 1986., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    Author: Keating, Dennis
  - Capital Investment or Community Development? - The Struggle for Control of Turf by Boston's Black and Latino Community. Boston, MA: UMASS Boston, 1986., Aug. 1986 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Author: Gaston, Mauricio; Kennedy, Marie
    Paper from the College of Public and Community Service, 44 pages
  - Comments on "downtown development". Boston, MA: UMASS Boston, Center for Community Planning, 1989., Aug. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Author: Kennedy, Marie
    Paper for the State of the Neighborhood Convention
  - Some thoughts on the Midtown Cultural District Plan. Boston, MA: UMASS Boston, Center for Community Planning, 1989., Feb. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Paper, 5 pages
  - Dudley in 2001 - After the El… Center for whom?. Boston, MA: UMASS Boston, College of Public and Community Service, 1985., Jan. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Author: Gaston, Mauricio; Kennedy, Marie; Gomes-Beach, Barbara; Kanter, Bonnie; Lescault, James; O'Meara, Mary; Sklar, Barbara
    Study of the Roxbury Action Program, analyses of Roxbury demographics and land control, charts included, 96 pages
  - Mixed Messages - A Brief Story of Columbia Point and U.S. Public Housing. Boston, MA: UMASS Boston, Center for Community Planning, 1989., Mar. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Essay to accompany "Columbia Point", a video slide transfer by Linda Swartz
  - Summary of the Urban Village Plan: temporary zoning for Boylston Street and West Fens. KAFNI, 1990., Sept. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Author: KAFNI
    Summary of plan - goals and intentions, 8 pages
  - A City Called Mandela - Secession and the Struggle for Community Control in Boston. Boston, MA: The North Star, No. 5, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Author: Kennedy, Marie; Tilly, Chris
  - Community Development Corporation of Boston (pamphlet). Boston, MA: CDC of Boston, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 48)
    Author: CDC of Boston
    Pamphlet/ booklet describing the CDC's operations and accomplishments, photos, written for residents - simple and straightforward, 4 pages
  - The Community Option: Institution-building and Reform in the Context of Local Regimes. 1997., Dec. 1997 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    Author: Wilson, Randall
    Paper/exam for Public Policy class - Community Political and Economic Development with Prof. Ramsay, 27 pages
  - The Politics of Community Capacity-Building - An Analysis of Boston's Enhanced Enterprise Community. 1996., 1996 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    Term paper for Public Policy class, 53 pages
  - Email to Pierre Clavel. 1999, Mar. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    Email with list of references on Boston development politics and attached papers, 2 pages
  - Pamphlet for EDAC: A Consortium of Concultants Specializing in Community Reinvestment Act Requirements, Minority Business Initiatives, and Community Economic Development. Boston, MA: EDAC, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 50)
    Author: EDAC
    Pamphlet describing the EDAC Areas of Expertise, 2 pages
  - Nuestra Vision de la Aldea Urbana. Boston, MA: DSNI, 1996., Sept. 1996 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Booklet in Spanish describing intentions of DSNI, 24 pages
  - Boston Group Pioneers Use of Eminent Domain. The Neighborhood Works, 12, No. 2. 1989., May-89 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Girard, Arthur
  - Dudley Neighbors, Inc. - Our Community Land Trust. Boston, MA: DSNI, 1990., May-90 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Document outlining Dudley Neighbors' structure and intentions, 4 pages
  - The Death and Life of Dudley - A lesson in urban economics. Boston, MA: The Boston Globe Magazine, 1990., Apr. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Boucher, Norman
    Magazine article, 12 pages
  - Eminent Domain Award Unique But Empowerment Goal Widely Shared. Boston, MA: Banker and Tradesman, 1989., Mar. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Handley, Ann
  - Model Homes for Welfare Families. The Ms. Reporter, 1989., Jul. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Suh, Mary
  - Dudley Street Group will renew area, not 'gentrify,' says director. Boston, MA: Dorchester Community News, 1989., Feb. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Pickering, Mark
  - Dudley Street renewal plans ratified by residents. Boston, MA: Dorchester Community News, 1989., Jun. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: [Author unknown]
  - Not a through street. Boston, MA: South End News, 1988., Aug. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Stalvey, J. G.
  - Dudley Street group aims for eminent domain rights. Boston, MA: Bay State Banner, 1988., Oct. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Havis, Devonya
  - Banking land - Dudley group wants to buy up land before the developers do. Boston, MA: South End News, 8, No. 38, 1987., Oct. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Planners seek funding to rebuild community. Boston, MA: Bay State Banner, 1987., Feb. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Martins, Gus
  - Hopes are High for Rebirth of Dudley Street Neighborhood. Boston, MA: Dorchester Argus-Citizen, 1987., Oct. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Sheffield, Reggie
  - Dudley Development plan moves ahead. Boston, MA: South End News, 11, No. 21, 1990., Jul. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Gus Newport: Salvaging Dudley Triangle. Boston, MA: Boston Business Journal, 1990., Apr. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Witt, Louise
  - State crisis, Dudley plans mark new year. Boston, MA: Dorchester Community News, 1990., Jan. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Uphams Corner needs eyed after Rix shutdown. Boston, MA: Dorchester Community News, 1991., Feb. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Hooping and hollering - The action is hot and heavy on local basketball courts. Boston, MA: South End News, 1991., Aug. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Fearnley, Elizabeth
  - Taking PRIDE. Boston, MA: South End News, 1991., Nov. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Dudley group builds pride in neighborhood. Boston, MA: Bay State Banner, 27, No. 8, 1991., Nov. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Dudley neighbors have PRIDE, ideas for change. Boston, MA: Dorchester Community News, 18, No.23, 1991., Dec. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Kanoff, Ilene
  - Dudley Triangle proposals advance under D.S.N.I. Boston, MA: Roxbury Community News, 1991., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Rowe, Owezo
  - Keeping the dealers away. Boston, MA: South End News, 1991., Aug. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Building an urban village: The Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative. Tacoma Park: Environmental Action, 28, No.1, 1996., 1996 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Sklar, Holly
  - Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative/Winthrop Estates. Chicago, IL: Planning, 63, No. 4, 1997., Apr. 1997 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Andrews, James
  - When activists win: The renaissance of Dudley St. New York, NY: The Nation, 264, 8, 1997., Mar. 1997 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Walljasper, Jay
    Journal article, 7 pages
  - Dudley Street neighborhood gathers to elect new leadership. Boston, MA: The Bay State Banner, 1997., Jul. 1997 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Batista, Elisa
  - A Neighborhood Starts to Recover from Decline. The Christian Science Monitor, 1994., Jun. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Spaid, Elisabeth
  - History and Observations. Boston, MA: The Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative, 1992., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Newport, Eugene Gus
    Paper on DSNI, 9 pages
  - Sustaining Community Power. Shelterforce, NHI, 1999., Feb. 1999 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Transforming Urban Regimes - A Grassroots Approach to Comprehensive Community Development: DSNI. Greensboro, NC: University of North Carolina, 1996., Aug. 1996 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Author: Tuloss, Janice
    Paper presented to American Political Science Association, SF, CA, 18 pages
  - DSNI Handout: To Find Out More…, late 1990s (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Handout with website and ways to order info packets and books on DSNI, 1 page
  - DSNI Mission and declaration of community rights. Boston, MA: DSNI, 1993., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Handouts describing DSNI's goals and community statements, 2 pages
  - Dudley Square Plan: A Strategy for Neighborhood Revitalization - Briefing Book. Boston, MA: DSNI, 1984., Dec. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Draft document with proposals for community development projects, maps and diagrams, 5- pages
  - Rebuilding Boston Information: Neighborhood Development Division. Boston, MA: City of Boston, [date unknown], [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 52)
    Document describing financing development projects and housing, 3 pages
  - Turning Problems into Opportunities. Boston, MA: CEDAC, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 14, Folder 53)
    Author: CEDAC
    Pamphlet describing CEDAC's development projects in Massachusetts, 3 pages
  - GBCD - Building Communities, Housing Completed. [date unknown - 1990s]., [date unknown - 1990s] (Box 14, Folder 54)
    Author: GBCD
    Folder of various pamphlets and documents - listing GBCD projects and pamphlets on its intents, approx. 25 pages
  - DSNI Historic Timeline. Boston, MA: DSNI, 1999., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    Timeline taken from website, 3 pages
  - Email to Pierre Clavel: searches on DSNI and Boston. Cornell University, 1999., Jan. 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: Donofrio, Greg
    Email with list of URLs for articles on DSNI and Boston, 16 pages
  - Bouncing back. Chicago, IL: Planning, 1998., Mar. 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Homsy, George
  - Real insurance: Greg Watson, Ros Everdell, and Tom McCullough of the Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative. New York, NY: Orion, 15, No. 4, 1996., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Chase, Steve; Hiestand, Emily
    Journal abstract, 1 page
  - Welfare "reform": Comin' up on the rough side of the mountain. Journal of Sociology and Social Welfare, 25, No. 1, 1998., 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Williams, LJ; Ward, R.; Davis, A.
  - A Community of Integrity - Building hope in the inner city of Boston. Sojourners, 24, No. 2, 1995., Jun. 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Meeker - Lowry, Susan
  - Recent Trends and Activities. Boston, MA: Warner and Stackpole LLP, 1996., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Mabel Louise Riley Foundation
    Document printed from internet describing Riley foundation's support of DSNI, 1 page
  - Dudley Street Initiative Creates an Urban Village. Boston, MA: CPN, 1999., 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: CPN
    Printed from internet - list of case studies and publications on DSNI, 7 pages
  - Citizen Participation, Neighborhood Planning and Empowerment of the Poor. NHI - Shelterforce Online, 1994., Aug. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Keating, W. Dennis
    Book reviews on works by Medoff, Sklar, Berry, Portney, and Thomson, 5 pages
  - Breaking Ground - A Report on Boston Housing Policy and Performance. Boston, MA: City of Boston, 1987., Apr. 1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Report on development, vacancies, housing, 81 pages
  - Nailing Down a Future. Boston, MA: Boston Globe Magazine, [date unknown - 1990s]., [date unknown - 1990s] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: Robb, Christina
    Magazine article, 4 pages
  - Boston Housing Partnership - Rental Program and Financing Options. Boston, MA: Boston Housing Partnership, 1986., Jan. 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: Boston Housing Partnership
    Various pamphlets and documents describing rental programs, BHP mission, and finances, 11 pages
  - Boston Affordable Housing Coalition - Steering Committee Meeting Agenda. Boston, Ma: BAHC, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: Boston Affordable Housing Coalition
    Meeting agenda for gathering at Harriet Tubman House, 1 page
  - HUD Tenants Score Major Victory, Delay Sale of Their Homes. Boston, MA: BAHC, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notification, 2 pages
  - Groups Assail HUD-Unit Sale Plans. Boston, MA: Dorchester Argus-Citizen, 1985., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Recommended Policy for Disposition of City-owned Property. Boston, MA: BAHC, [date unknown]., [date unknown] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: BAHC
    Document with policy descriptions, 2 pages
  - Various documents. Boston, MA: BAHC, 1984 - 1985., Apr. 1984 - Oct. 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Documents: Proposals for organizational structure, committee reports on housing, internal organizational memos, letters to Flynn, tax plan tables, CHD report, policy recommendations, 9 separate documents, approx. 50 pages total
  - In Boston, South Africa - the issue is the same. Boston, MA: Boston Business Journal, 1985., Journal article, 1 page (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Journal article
  - Fifty Percent Solution? Flynn, developers clash on low-income housing. Boston, MA: Boston TAB, 1984., Dec. 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: Luberoff, David
  - The Neighborhood Housing Fund. Boston, MA: Housing Committee, [date unknown]., [date unknown - 1980s] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: Kelly, James
    Pamphlet describing NHF, letter to citizens, 5 pages
  - Update on Developments. Boston, MA: Community News, 1984., Apr. 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: Community News
    Articles on housing developments, 2 pages
  - Email to Pierre Clavel: info on CCCD. 1999., Jul. 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Author: Branfman, Judy
    Email describing CCCD - timeline and suggested articles, descriptions, 3 pages
  - Proceedings - Agenda and Pamphlet for State of the Neighborhoods Convention. Boston, MA: Center for Community Action, Coalition for Community Control of Development, Episcopal City Mission, 1989., Apr. 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Pamphlet describing CCS, CCCD, and ECM achievements and goals, 38 pages.
  - Linkage - Affordable Homes and Jobs. Boston, MA: BRA, 1988., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Newsletter of the BRA 'Building Bridges of Opportunity', 12 pages
  - Breaking New Ground: Boston's Affordable Housing Initiatives. Boston, MA: City of Boston, [date unknown - 1980s]., [date unknown - 1980s] (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Pamphlet for National League of Cities Annual Conference, 10 pages
  - Various documents. Boston, MA: Boston Housing Partnership, 1985., c. 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Documents describing the Boston Housing Partnership: rental programs, map of CDCs, goals summary, media features, 9 separate documents, approx. 17 pages